Guide to the Collective Bargaining Agreements WAG.346
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Collective Bargaining Agreements
1946-1993
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
WAG.346
1 linear foot in 1 record carton.
The Collective Bargaining Agreements (1946-1993) contains documentation from major labor unions within the United States. The materials available in this collection consist of by-laws, summaries of member benefits, and annual program reports from media, entertainment, hospitality, fashion, graphic arts, and local state labor councils within the United States. A significant portion of the collection consists of agreements made between the Newspaper Guild of New York, Local No. 3, of the American Newspaper Guild and other New York State publishers. The collection also features agreements established between the American Newspaper Guild and the International News Service, Department of The Hearst Corporation and the International News Photos. The collection also includes agreements established between the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) and other affiliated unions.
Scope and Contents
The Collective Bargaining Agreements contains documentation from major labor unions within the United States. These materials include by-laws, summaries of member benefits, and annual program reports from media, entertainment, hospitality, fashion, graphic arts, and local state labor councils within the United States. A significant portion of the collection consists of agreements made between the Newspaper Guild of New York, Local No. 3, of the American Newspaper Guild and other New York State publishers. The collection also features agreements established between the American Newspaper Guild and the International News Service, Department of The Hearst Corporation and the International News Photos. The collection also includes agreements established between the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) and other affiliated unions.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. Original order is unknown.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
There is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials. The accession number associated with this collection is 2017.064.
Collective bargaining -- United States.; Labor unions -- United States.; Journalists -- Labor unions.; Actors -- Labor unions -- United States.; Collective labor agreements.; AFL-CIO; American Newspaper Guild; Newspaper Guild of New York
- Newspaper Guild of New York, 1946-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
- American Newspaper Guild, 1946-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- Actors' Equity Association, 1962-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- San Francisco-Oakland Newspaper Guild, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Newspaper Guild, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1949-05 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1968-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Moving Picture Machine Operators, Union Local 306, 1951-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Masters, Mates, and Pilots (MM&P), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- New York City Central Labor Council, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Graphic Arts International Union, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- North Jersey Newspaper Guild, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Gannett Company -- Utica Observer-Dispatch, Utica Daily Press, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Transport Workers Union of America, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1954-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Communications Workers of America, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- National Maritime Union of America, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Local 32B, Service Employees International Union, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Office of Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Department of Labor of the City of New York, 1957-06 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Career and Salary Plan -- New York City Employees -- The City of New York, Department of Personnel, 1960-05-01 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Occucopy, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)